(Leonard:)Just like you.
(Penny:)I'm just saying,
you pretend you don't,
(Penny:)but you have feelings
just like everybody else.
(Sheldon:)Not true. No, look at me.
(Sheldon:)I had an engagement
ring to give a girl,
(Sheldon:)and instead,
she rejected me.
(Sheldon:)And am I emotional
about that? No.
(Sheldon:)No, I am sitting here
on a couch,
(Sheldon:)talking about my
favorite TV character
(Sheldon:)like nothing happened.
'Cause I am just like him:
all logical, all the time.
(Penny:)Sweetie, you're yelling.
(Sheldon:)Because when I speak
at a regular volume,
(Sheldon:)no one seems to believe me
(Sheldon:)that I've put
this Amy nonsense behind me!
(door slams)
(Wil:)This documentary
is gonna be awesome.
(Mr Rostenkowski:)You gonna be okay down here?
Yeah. Yeah,
(Howard:)I feel like
an archaeologist.
Indiana Jones and
the Single-Family Dwelling.
Hey. Look!
(Howard:)Found a seashell.
(Mr Rostenkowski:)Yeah, that's a rat skull.
(shrieks)
(Mr Rostenkowski:)Relax.
(Mr Rostenkowski:)There's enough droppings down
here without you making more.